eoshampoo.com 2011-06-17

# Privacy Policy - EO Products

### Your Privacy

Thank you for shopping at eoproducts.com. Ensuring the privacy and security of your personal information is very important to us. Our privacy and security policy outlines the information we collect about you, how and why we use the information and the choices you have to restrict our usage of this information.

### Collected Information

Personal information you provide to us while creating or updating an account and at checkout (ie: name, address, telephone number, email address, billing address, ship-to address and credit card information) is maintained in private files on our secure web server and on our internal systems.

We may disclose specific personal information about you if required by law, governmental request, court order if based on our good faith belief, it is necessary to conform or comply with such law, request or court.

### Our Newsletter List

We offer those who sign-up for our newsletter advanced notice of sales, new products and special offers. Email addresses collected at are only used internally. We respect your privacy rights and will not sell or rent your email address to other companies. If you would like to be removed from our email list, please follow the instructions sent along with each email. We will remove your name from our email list as soon as possible. Please recognize that you may receive another email before we are able to remove you.

### Secure Shopping

EO Products uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. EOProducts.com uses Secure SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) to encrypt information like Credit Card details. Any contact information obtained for the purpose of this web site will be stored solely in a secure database. No one other than EO Products will have access to your information. Under no circumstances will your contact information be sold, published, or disclosed to any party or company. EO Products do not store Credit Card information on our servers.

### Policy Changes

We may periodically update this privacy & security policy for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed. Any changes made will be posted here. By visiting our website you agree to accept any changes made to this policy. Our privacy & security policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our website.

Please contact us with any questions about our privacy & security policy:

  * By E-Mail: [inf@eoproducts.com](mailto:inf@eoproducts.com?subject=)
  * By Phone: 800-570-3775
